{
    "id": "e99289204aa94d4a93788262be26f13b",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Everything ...................... he said was wrong.",
            "description": "After quantifiers like all, every and everything, we prefer that to which.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "...................... she said made me angry.",
            "description": "What means the things which.",
            "answers": [
                "That",
                "Which",
                "What"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Everybody .......................... arrived.",
            "description": "After expressions like every, everyone and everybody we use a singular verb.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "is",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If you ................. happen to finish early, give me a ring.",
            "description": "We use should happen in the if-clause to suggest that something is very unlikely. ",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If she should be late, we .................... have to leave without her.",
            "description": "Would is uncommon in the main clause after 'if...should'.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The thing ........................ happened next horrified me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My jeans ....................... too tight for me.",
            "description": "The noun jeans is plural and has no singular form. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A lot of social problems ........................... caused by poverty.",
            "description": "If the noun following 'a lot of' is plural, we use a plural verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A lot of time ............................ required to learn a language.",
            "description": "If the noun following 'a lot of' is singular, we use a singular verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "'We have got only two liters of milk left.' '............................. not enough.'",
            "description": "When we talk about amounts and quantities, we often use singular verbs. ",
            "answers": [
                "That is",
                "Those are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You are too ....................... to be a soldier.",
            "description": "We use small to refer to size. ",
            "answers": [
                "small",
                "little"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ...................... hot that we stopped playing.",
            "description": "Very and too cannot be followed by a that-clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "very",
                "too",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}